(Penny:)Spider-Man. Get him Spider-Man.
(Sheldon:)Amazing Spider-Man, Ultimate Spider-Man,
Spectacular Spider-Man...
(Sheldon:)...The Marvelous Adventures of Spider-Man,
Spider-Man 2099?
- Leonard?
LEONARD: This can go on all night.
(Leonard:)Why don't you just come with us?
(Penny:)Ugh. That's what I was trying to avoid.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I forgot Sensational Spider-Man.
(Penny:)Oh, what a cute little store.
(Penny:)Everybody's staring at me.
LEONARD: Don't worry. They're more
scared of you than you are of them.
(Penny:)Unlikely.
(Penny:)Here. What about this one
for my nephew?
- A superb choice.
- Oh, great.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, provided he has already read
Infinite Crisis and 52...
(Sheldon:)...and is familiar with the reestablishment
of the DC Multiverse.
Uh, what's a Multiverse?
(Sheldon:)Get her out of here.